Guide to the Dr. Huey P. Newton Foundation Inc. Collection
Department of Special Collections
- Series 2: Black Panther Party Records, 2
  - Subseries 10: Miscellaneous, 10
    - [Address Books, n.d.] [2 of 3] (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - [Address Books, n.d.] [3 of 3] (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - [Address Book - 1973]1973 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - [Address Book - 1977/78]1977/78 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - [Appointment Calendar - 1974]1974 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - [Appointment Calendar - 1975]1975 (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - [Appointment Calendar - 1976 - 1978]1976; 1978 (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - [Appointment Calendar - 1979 - 1980]1979; 1980 (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - [Diary, n.d] (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - Portrait of unidentified man [art original] / Ronnie Newton, pencil on paper (Othertype 62, Folder 1)
- Series 3: David Hilliard, 3
  - Subseries 1: Correspondence, 1
    - David (General File) [1 of 2]1972 - 1975 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      articles, testimony by Sandy Turner
    - David (General File) [2 of 2]1972 - 1975 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      rules violation reports by DH
    - [The Community of Concern for David Hilliard ] [1 of 3]1972 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      petitions gathering names, reference lists, reference letters sent to various people signed by Jane Fonda and Tom Hayden, letters from various people supporting David Hilliard
    - [The Community of Concern for David Hilliard ] [2 of 3]1972 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      petitions gathering names, reference lists, letters from various people supporting David Hilliard
    - [The Community of Concern for David Hilliard ] [3 of 3]1972 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - [The Community of Concern for David Hilliard IIa] [1 of 3]1969 - 1972 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - [The Community of Concern for David Hilliard IIa] [2 of 3]1969 - 1972 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - [The Community of Concern for David Hilliard IIa] [3 of 3]1969 - 1972 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - [The Community of Concern for David Hilliard IIb - Individual Letters] [1 of 2]1972 (Box 1, Folder 9)
      letters from various people supporting David Hilliard
    - [The Community of Concern for David Hilliard IIb - Individual Letters] [2 of 2]1972 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Community for Concern for David HIlliard [1 of 2]1972 - 1974 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      letters of support, "Fact Sheet on David Hilliard", list of concerned citizens listed according to professions,
    - Community for Concern for David HIlliard [2 of 2]1972 - 1974 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      letters of support, list of concerned citizens listed according to professions,
    - Community of Concern for David Hilliard #2 [1 of 2]1972 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      letters of support, list of concerned citizens listed according to professions
    - Community of Concern for David Hilliard #2 [2 of 2]1972 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      letters of support
    - The Community of Concern for David Hilliard [permission forms with names, titles and addresses] [1 of 4]1972 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - The Community of Concern for David Hilliard [permission forms with names, titles and addresses] [2 of 4]1972 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - The Community of Concern for David Hilliard [permission forms with names, titles and addresses] [3 of 4]1972 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - The Community of Concern for David Hilliard [permission forms with names, titles and addresses] [4 of 4]1972 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - The Community of Concern for David Hilliard (Box 2, Folder 9)
      list of supporters according to their professions
    - Book receipts titles sent to D.H. in prison - 19731973 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence to David Hilliard re: Expulsion 4/24/741974 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Misc + David at Vacaville1972 - 1974 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - David Hilliard's Prison / Parole Correspondence [1 of 3]1972 - 1974 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      prison evaluations and records
    - David Hilliard's Prison / Parole Correspondence [2 of 3]1972 - 1974 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - David Hilliard's Prison / Parole Correspondence [3 of 3]1972 - 1974 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - David Hilliard - Prison/Parole Correspondence1972 - 1974 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      prison records and examinations, Northern California Ecumenical Council, Berkeley Society of Friends
  - Subseries 2: Legal, 2
    - Hilliard, David et al. v. Perini Corp. & BART P.I. 7-7-69 9457 JH 7-691969 - 1970 (Box 3, Folder 5)
      claim for damages from an auto accident
    - People v. David Hilliard [1 of 3]1969 (Box 3, Folder 6)
      No. C 18383 volume I;Reporter's Transcript of Proceedings Department #2, Municipal Court, Berkeley, California;December 8,9,19, & 11, 1969
    - People v. David Hilliard [2 of 3]1969 (Box 3, Folder 7)
      No. C 18383 volume II;Reporter's Transcript of Proceedings Department #2, Municipal Court, Berkeley, California;December 8,9,10, & 11, 1969
    - People v. David Hilliard [3 of 3]1969 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - People v. David Hilliard [1 of 2]1969 (Box 3, Folder 9)
      No. C 18383 volume III;Reporter's Transcript of Proceedings Department #2, Municipal Court, Berkeley, California;December 8,9,10, & 11, 1969
    - People v. David Hilliard [2 of 2]1969 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Hilliard, David People v. (PC 148. Oakland Muni #C 22154) #9546 G/P (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Hilliard, David Peo vs. On Appeal #9280 G1969 - 1972 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Hilliard, David vs. Mitchell et al. U.S.D.C. Civil Rts Suit #9747 G [1 of 2]1970 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Hilliard, David vs. Mitchell et al. U.S.D.C. Civil Rts Suit #9747 G [2 of 2]1970 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Hilliard, David (Expert) Witness File 9680 (1) [1 of 2] (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Hilliard, David (Expert) Witness File 9680 (1) [2 of 2] (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Hilliard, David - U.S. vs. (1) Appeal 9680 BD [1 of 3]1969 - 1972 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Hilliard, David - U.S. vs. (1) Appeal 9680 BD [2 of 3]1969 - 1972 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Hilliard, David - U.S. vs. (1) Appeal 9680 BD [3 of 3]1969 - 1972 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Hilliard, U.S. v (2) Record on Appeal 96801969 - 1971 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - U.S. v. Hilliard (3) Mandate 9680 [1 of 2] (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - U.S. v. Hilliard (3) Mandate 9680 [2 of 2] (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Hilliard, David U.S. vs. (4) Research and Related Material #9680 [1 of 2]1969 - 1970 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Hilliard, David U.S. vs. (4) Research and Related Material #9680 [2 of 2]1969 - 1970 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - U.S. v. Hilliard Re: Wiretap #5 9680 [1 of 3]1971 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - U.S. v. Hilliard Re: Wiretap #5 9680 [2 of 3]1971 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - U.S. v. Hilliard Re: Wiretap #5 9680 [3 of 3]1971 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Hilliard, U.S. v. (6) Wiretap Extra Copies 9680 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Hilliard, David U.S. v. Appeal (7)Amicus Curaie Brief 9680 [1 of 2]1971 - 1972 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Hilliard, David U.S. v. Appeal (7)Amicus Curaie Brief 9680 [2 of 2]1971 - 1972 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - U.S. v. Hilliard: Jury Selection 9680 (10) [1 of 2] (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - U.S. v. Hilliard: Jury Selection 9680 (10) [2 of 2] (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Hilliard, David U.S.v Correspondence #9680 G (12) (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Hilliard, David, U.S. v. Press #9680 G (13) (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Hilliard, David U.S. v. Travel #9680 G (14)1969 - 1970 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Hilliard, David U.S. vs. Pre-trial Motions 9680 [1 of 3] (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Hilliard, David U.S. vs. Pre-trial Motions 9680 [2 of 3] (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Hilliard, David U.S. vs. Pre-trial Motions 9680 [3 of 3] (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Hilliard, David, U.S. v. 18 USC - 871 - Threats Against Pres. Indictment & Bail #9680 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Hilliard, David #9680 U.S. v. Hilliard Law & Research & Evidence [1 of 2]1970 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Hilliard, David #9680 U.S. v. Hilliard Law & Research & Evidence [2 of 2]1970 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - David Hilliard - Conn Wiretap Case Inform [1 of 2]1971 - 1979 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - David Hilliard - Conn Wiretap Case Inform [2 of 2]1971 - 1979 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Supreme Court of the U.S. Hilliard Wiretap Case1971 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - [ U.S. v. David Hilliard ] [1 of 3]1971 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      Motion File; --Dismiss Indictment (2); --Bill of Particulars; --Counsel to Conduct Jury Voir Dire; --Limine; --Inspection & Disc; --Challenging Grand and Petit Jury
    - [ U.S. v. David Hilliard ] [2 of 3]1971 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - [ U.S. v. David Hilliard ] [3 of 3]1971 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Hilliard, David Peo. V. 2) Appeal 8821 AB [1 of 2]1971 - 1972 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Hilliard, David Peo. V. 2) Appeal 8821 AB [2 of 2]1971 - 1972 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Hilliard, David (3) Appeal General Correspondence BD/AB 8821[1 of 2]1971 - 1972 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Hilliard, David (3) Appeal General Correspondence BD/AB 8821[2 of 2]1971 - 1972 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Hilliard, David 4)Appeal Briefs 8821 GER 1972 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Hilliard, David - POPE Writ of Habeas Corpus/Funeral #6 8821 1972 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Hilliard, David Peo. V. (7) Hallinan's File 8821 AB [1 of 3]1968 - 1971 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Hilliard, David Peo. V. (7) Hallinan's File 8821 AB [2 of 3]1968 - 1971 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Hilliard, David Peo. V. (7) Hallinan's File 8821 AB [3 of 3]1968 - 1971 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Hilliard, David 10. Adult Authority Authorizations 8821 AB1972 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Hilliard, David Peo v. (1)New Trial, Bail on Appeal 8821 AB [1 of 4]1971 - 1972 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Hilliard, David Peo v. (1)New Trial, Bail on Appeal 8821 AB [2 of 4]1971 - 1972 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Hilliard, David Peo v. (1)New Trial, Bail on Appeal 8821 AB [3 of 4]1971 - 1972 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Hilliard, David Peo v. (1)New Trial, Bail on Appeal 8821 AB [4 of 4]1971 - 1972 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Hilliard, David U.S. v. (False Statements) (2) Pretrial Motions 10721 BD (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Hilliard, David U.S. v. (False Statements) (3) Extra Copies / Pleadings 10721 AB (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Hilliard, David U.S. v. False Statements (4) 1972 Grand Jury 10721 BD [1 of 2] (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Hilliard, David U.S. v. False Statements (4) 1972 Grand Jury 10721 BD [2 of 2] (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Hilliard, David U.S. v. False Statements- (5) govt's list of witnesses & docs 10721 AB [1 of 2] (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Hilliard, David U.S. v. False Statements- (5) govt's list of witnesses & docs 10721 AB [2 of 2] (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Hilliard, David U.S. v. False Statements 10721 BD [1 of 2] (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Hilliard, David U.S. v. False Statements 10721 BD [2 of 2] (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - [People v. David Hilliard - Petition for Hearing]1972 [?] (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - [People v Hilliard - Appeal] (Box 10, Folder 1)
      People of the State of California v. David Hilliard, Court of Appeal of the State of California, First Appellate District, Division Two;No. 1 Crim. 10184
    - People v. Hilliard, David - Appellant's Opening Brief [1 of 2] (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - People v. Hilliard, David - Appellant's Opening Brief [2 of 2] (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - People v. David Hilliard - Appellant's Opening Brief (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Hilliard, David Re: Archie Henderson Sacramento Habeas Corpus 10693 [1 of 4]1972 - 1974 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Hilliard, David Re: Archie Henderson Sacramento Habeas Corpus 10693 [2 of 4]1972 - 1974 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Hilliard, David Re: Archie Henderson Sacramento Habeas Corpus 10693 [3 of 4]1972 - 1974 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Hilliard, David Re: Archie Henderson Sacramento Habeas Corpus 10693 [4 of 4]1972 - 1974 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Hilliard v. Calif. Adult Authority # 13419 index (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Research #13419 (1) (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence to / from Charlie and Mel #13419 (2) (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Hilliard- A.G. Affidavits #13419 (3) (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Letters - from Central File #13419 (4) (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Misc. - Adult Authority #13419 (5) (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Evaluations at Time of A.A. Hearing # 13419 (6) (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Hilliard, David 12. Medical Problems at Folsom (7) #13419 BD (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Hilliard, David adv. The People #13419 AB 5) Proceedings before Adult Authority #13419 AB (8) (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Personal Reports and Classification #13419 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Select Senate Committee on Penal Institutions #13419 (10) (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Memorandum re: Judicial Review of A.A. #13419 (11) (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - In re Robert Storm - Habeas #13419 (12) (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Olson et al. v. Pope et al. (13) (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Hilliard, David - Internal Revenue Matter 9760 AB [CRG]1970 - 1975 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Hilliard v. Calif. Adult Authority (Solano Co.) Superior Court No. 9987 #13419 CRG [1 of 3]1973 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Hilliard v. Calif. Adult Authority (Solano Co.) Superior Court No. 9987 #13419 CRG [2 of 3]1973 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Hilliard v. Calif. Adult Authority (Solano Co.) Superior Court No. 9987 #13419 CRG [3 of 3]1973 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Hilliard, Patricia In re: on behalf of David Hilliard on Habeas Corpus (1973) #13419 CRG [1 of 3]1973 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Hilliard, Patricia In re: on behalf of David Hilliard on Habeas Corpus (1973) #13419 CRG [2 of 3]1973 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Hilliard, Patricia In re: on behalf of David Hilliard on Habeas Corpus (1973) #13419 CRG [3 of 3]1973 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Hilliard v. Calif. Adult Authority (Solano Co.) Superior Court No. 9987 13419 CRG [1 of 3]1974 - 1975 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Hilliard v. Calif. Adult Authority (Solano Co.) Superior Court No. 9987 13419 CRG [2 of 3]1974 - 1975 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Hilliard v. Calif. Adult Authority (Solano Co.) Superior Court No. 9987 13419 CRG [3 of 3]1974 - 1975 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Hilliard v. Calif. 13419 CRG Adult Authority (Solano Co.) Superior Court No. 9987 [1 of 3]1972 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Hilliard v. Calif. 13419 CRG Adult Authority (Solano Co.) Superior Court No. 9987 [2 of 3]1972 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Hilliard v. Calif. 13419 CRG Adult Authority (Solano Co.) Superior Court No. 9987 [3 of 3]1972 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - David Hilliard vs. Dr. T.R. Clanon1974; 1971 - 1974 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Hilliard, David v. Clannon, T.L. No. C-73-1750 - US Dist Ct 7-19-77 #13419 777-27CRG [1 of 4]1977 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Hilliard, David v. Clannon, T.L. No. C-73-1750 - US Dist Ct 7-19-77 #13419 777-27CRG [2 of 4]1977 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Hilliard, David v. Clannon, T.L. No. C-73-1750 - US Dist Ct 7-19-77 #13419 777-27CRG [3 of 4]1977 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Hilliard, David v. Clannon, T.L. No. C-73-1750 - US Dist Ct 7-19-77 #13419 777-27CRG [4 of 4]1977 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Hilliard, David v. Clannon, T.L. No. 74--3121 US CT. Of Appeals #13419 7-19-77 777-27 CRG [1 of 2] 1977 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Hilliard, David v. Clannon, T.L. No. 74--3121 US CT. Of Appeals #13419 7-19-77 777-27 CRG [2 of 2] 1977 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Hilliard V. Clannon (federal) 777-27 CRG Appellate Proceedings Re Habeas closed 7-19-77 #13419 [1 of 3]1977 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Hilliard V. Clannon (federal) 777-27 CRG Appellate Proceedings Re Habeas closed 7-19-77 #13419 [2 of 3]1977 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Hilliard V. Clannon (federal) 777-27 CRG Appellate Proceedings Re Habeas closed 7-19-77 #13419 [3 of 3]1977 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Pleadings [1 of 3] (Box 14, Folder 5)
      No. 71-1105
    - Pleadings [2 of 3] (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Pleadings [3 of 3] (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - David Hilliard (case) [1 of 3]1971 - 1974 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - David Hilliard (case) [2 of 3]1971 - 1974 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - David Hilliard (case) [3 of 3]1971 - 1974 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Probation Reports on David Hilliard 6-30-711968 - 1971 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - David Hilliard - Parole Application1972 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - DH Parole File [1 of 3]1972 - 1973 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - DH Parole File [2 of 3]1972 - 1973 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - DH Parole File [3 of 3]1972 - 1973 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Hilliard, David Personal & Press 8021 Dec. 1969 (8)1968 - 1970 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Hilliard, David People v. Ala Cty. Correspondence & Memos #88211968 - 1973 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Hilliard, David Prison Letters 4-1-72 [1 of 3] 1972 - 1973 (Box 15, Folder 10)
      Includes "The Community of Concern for David Hilliard"
    - Hilliard, David Prison Letters 4-1-72 [2 of 3] 1972 - 1973 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Hilliard, David Prison Letters 4-1-72 [3 of 3] 1972 - 1973 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - David Hilliard - Prison File (Includes S. Turner Files and correspondence) 12-9-74 [1 of 4]1972 - 1974 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - David Hilliard - Prison File (Includes S. Turner Files and correspondence) 12-9-74 [2 of 4]1972 - 1974 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - David Hilliard - Prison File (Includes S. Turner Files and correspondence) 12-9-74 [3 of 4]1972 - 1974 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - David Hilliard - Prison File (Includes S. Turner Files and correspondence) 12-9-74 [4 of 4]1972 - 1974 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Subseries 3: Manuscripts, 3
    - David Hilliard Autobiography [1 of 2]1975 (Box 16, Folder 5)
      "Facing the Nation: The Autobiography of David Hilliard with the assistance of Hans Steinkellner [111+ pages]
    - David Hilliard Autobiography [2 of 2]1975 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Misc. Information on David's Book 1994 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Series 4: Freedom of Information Act files
  - FBI Files: Tap Logs 19691969 - 1970 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Phone log, March 12, 19691969 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Phone log, March 13, 19691969; 1990 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Phone log, March 14, 19691969; 1990 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Phone log, March 15, 19691969; 1990 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Phone log, March 16, 19691969 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Phone log, March 17, 19691969 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Phone log, March 18, 19691969 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Phone log, March 19, 19691969 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Phone log, March 20, 19691969 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Phone log, March 21, 19691969 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Phone log, March 22, 19691969 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Phone log, March 24, 19691969 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Phone log, March 26, 19691969 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Phone log, March 27, 19691969 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Phone log, March 29, 19691969 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Phone log, March 31, 19691969 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Phone log, April 7, 19691969 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Phone log, April 23, 19691969 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Phone log, April 24, 19691969 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Phone log, April 25, 19691969 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Phone log, April 26, 19691969 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Phone log, April 27, 19691969 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Phone log, May 8, 19691969 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Phone log, May 9, 19691969 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Phone log, May 10, 19691969 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Phone log, May 11, 19691969 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Phone log, May 12, 19691969 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Phone log, May 13, 19691969 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Phone log, May 14, 19691969 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Phone log, May 15, 19691969 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Phone log, May 27, 19691969 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Phone log, May 28, 19691969 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Phone log, May 29, 19691969 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Phone log, May 30, 19691969 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Phone log, May 31, 19691969 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Phone log, June 1, 19691969 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Phone log, June 2, 19691969 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Phone log, June 3, 19691969 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Phone log, June 4, 19691969 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Phone log, June 5, 19691969 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Phone log, June 6, 19691969 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Phone log, June 10, 19691969 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Phone log, June 12, 19691969 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Phone log, June 18, 19691969 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Phone log, June 19, 19691969 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Phone log, June 20, 19691969 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Phone log, June 21, 19691969 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Phone log, June 23, 19691969 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Phone log, June 24, 19691969 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Phone log, June 25, 19691969 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Phone log, June 26, 19691969 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Phone log, June 27, 19691969 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Phone log, June 28, 19691969 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Phone log, June 29, 19691969 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Phone log, June 30, 19691969 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Phone log, July 1, 19691969 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Phone log, July 2, 19691969 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Phone log, July 3, 19691969 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Phone log, July 4, 19691969 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Phone log, July 5, 19691969 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Phone log, July 6, 19691969 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Phone log, July 7, 19691969 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Phone log, July 8, 19691969 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Phone log, July 9, 19691969 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Phone log, July 10, 19691969 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Phone log, July 11, 19691969 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Phone log, July 12, 19691969 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Phone log, July 13, 19691969 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Phone log, July 14, 19691969 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Phone log, July 15, 19691969 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Phone log, July 16, 19691969 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Phone log, July 17, 19691969 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Phone log, July 18, 19691969 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Phone log, July 22, 19691969 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Phone log, July 23, 19691969 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Phone log, July 26, 19691969 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Phone log, July 28, 19691969 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Phone log, July 29, 19691969 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Phone log, July 30, 19691969 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Phone log, July 31, 19691969 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Phone log, August 1, 19691969 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Phone log, August 2, 19691969 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Phone log, August 3, 19691969 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Phone log, August 4, 19691969 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Phone log, August 5, 19691969 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Phone log, August 6, 19691969 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Phone log, August 7, 19691969 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Phone log, August 8, 19691969 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Phone log, August 9, 19691969 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Phone log, August 10, 19691969 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Phone log, August 11, 19691969 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Phone log, August 12, 19691969 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Phone log, August 13, 19691969 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Phone log, August 14, 19691969 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Phone log, August 15, 19691969 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Phone log, August 16, 19691969 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Phone log, August 18, 19691969 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Phone log, August 19, 19691969 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Phone log, August 20, 19691969 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Phone log, August 23, 19691969 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Phone log, August 25, 19691969 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Phone log, August 26, 19691969 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Phone log, August 30, 19691969 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Phone log, August 31, 19691969 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Phone log, September 1, 19691969 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Phone log, September 3, 19691969 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Phone log, September 4, 19691969 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Phone log, September 5, 19691969 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Phone log, September 6, 19691969 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Phone log, September 7, 19691969 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Phone log, September 8, 19691969 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Phone log, September 9, 19691969 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Phone log, September 10, 19691969 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Phone log, September 11, 19691969 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Phone log, September 12, 19691969 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Phone log, September 13, 19691969 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Phone log, September 14, 19691969 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Phone log, September 15, 19691969 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Phone log, September 16, 19691969 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Phone log, September 17, 19691969 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Phone log, September 18, 19691969 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Phone log, September 19, 19691969 (Box 3, Folder 28)